Oh, come on, Melissa.
How long are you gonna
keep punishing me for this?
Okay, okay.
Once again, uh, I did not technically
have sex with your mother.
You wanna catch me up?
Well, you know Alan
was nailing his receptionist, right?
Yeah.
Apparently, she caught him in bed
with her mother.
What do you know?
I've been calling him that for years,
and now he's up and done it.
I was not responsible for my actions.
I was stoned out of my mind.
You know, that excuse
has never once worked for me.
Me neither, cops or boyfriends.
No. Hey, hey, hey.
Your mother put enough pot
in that banana bread...
...to treat every case of glaucoma
in the San Fernando Valley.
I have a recipe for macaroons,
very similar.
I was so high,
I didn't even know who she was.
We were just colors.
I was red, she was blue.
We were trying to make purple.
My phone's dead.
Could I borrow your cell?
- Sure, it's on the coffee table.
- Thanks.
So bottom line, I was drugged
and molested by your mother...
...and I'm the bad guy.
Man, how many times
have I heard you make this phone call?
Yeah, who'd have thought
of the two of us...
...I'd be the one to end up
in a healthy, stable relationship?
Who is Rachel,
and why is she sending you topless photos?
- Uh...
- Yeah, who'd have thought?
You wanna explain to me why this woman
is sending you naked pictures of herself?
I'd love to explain it.
- Go ahead.
- I said I'd love to, I didn't say I could.
- Are you sleeping with her?
- No. No, of course not.
Then why the pictures?
Uh... Well, my best guess would be that,
like a lot of girls...
...she wanted to show off
her new boob job.
That's your best guess?
Well, you wouldn't understand...
...because clearly,
God has blessed you with this great bounty.
- Damn it, Charlie, I want to know-
- Excuse me, I'm on the phone.
- Shh. Alan's on the phone.
- Don't shush me. Who is this Rachel?
Nobody, really.
I used to go out with her
way, way before you and I met...
...and I fell so deeply in love.
Head over heels in love,
puppy-dog love. Woof.
Hang on, Melissa.
I couldn't hear anything
after "you son of a bitch."
- Does this Rachel know you're engaged?
- Um...
Think long and hard
before you start lying to me.
I was. That's why I said, "Um..."
- Charlie.
- She doesn't know.
Why not?
Boy, you're gonna keep this flapjack
on the griddle, aren't you?
- Berta, would you give us a minute?
- Oh, you're gonna need more than a minute.
So long. I'm gonna miss you.
What are you talking about?
She's not going anywhere, are you?
Where are you going? Chelsea.
- Chelsea, wait.
- Can't we just put this behind us?
I swear, I'll never make out
with your mother again.
Let's face it, Charlie. We both knew
you were gonna blow it eventually.
I didn't.
I had my suspicions, but I wasn't sure.
I wish I could say the same. Goodbye.
- Oh, please don't leave.
- Oh, please don't hang up.
ALAN & CHARLIE:
I love you.
And I love you too.
Sure you don't want a drink?
No. When I'm depressed,
alcohol just makes me feel worse.
Yeah, see, the trick is to drink past that.
It's not a sprint, it's a marathon.
You ever think we're both doomed
to grow old alone and unloved?
A couple of pathetic bachelors
with no one to talk to but each other?
You ought to do ads for this stuff.
So you gonna tell me what happened
with Chelsea?
I can show you.
Chelsea found this on my phone.
I ask you,
is that worth breaking an engagement?
It's worth breaking a spine.
- Were you sleeping with this girl?
- No, no. She just sent me a few pictures.
Oh, well, then why did you keep them?
All right, all right, all right.
But you gotta understand
the message that this sends to Chelsea.
Other than, you know:
"Got milk."
- But I'm not cheating.
- There are other forms of cheating.
There's flirting,
there's fantasizing about other women.
- Oh, come on. Fantasizing is not cheating.
- To women it is.
They don't like the idea that you're
mentally replacing them with someone else.
What if I'm mentally supplementing them
with someone else?
You know, like I'm making love to Chelsea,
and in my mind...
...Rachel here is just helping out.
She does look very helpful.
Nevertheless, I can understand
why Chelsea would take a dimmer view.
Yeah, well, I think she overreacted.
In fact, I think she owes me an apology.
You're just gonna sit here
and wait till she comes crawling back?
Yes, I am.
And then, because hell
will long since have frozen over...
...we can go ice-skating.
It's good that you have a plan.
Now, if you will pardon me...
...I have to go pick up Jake
at his mother's.
Oh, good. Just what we need
to brighten up our weekend.
A large, sullen teenager
with gas and questionable hygiene.
There's nothing questionable about it.
There we go.
Over the hump.
JUDITH: She's my mother, Herb.
I want her here when I have the baby.
Well, I don't need yet another woman
in this house yelling at me...
...calling me an idiot.
JUDITH:
My mother doesn't yell, you idiot.
I'm gonna let that pass
because you're pregnant.
JUDITH:
Don't you dare blame this on hormones.
What's my alternative, Judith?
Accept the fact that I'm an idiot?
- Oh, hey, Alan.
- Is this a bad time?
They're all bad.
Seven and a half months of bad.
JUDITH: Don't you walk away from me.
- Oh, I'm sorry, I was answering the door.
That's what we idiots do
when we hear a doorbell.
Hi, Dad. Bye, Mom. Good luck, Herb.
Bye, Jake. Wish I was going with you.
I knew it
as soon as it came out of my mouth.
I could get used to this.
Don't.
As far as Charlie's concerned,
mi casa es mi casa.
All right, I've ordered your pizza.
I'm going home.
Thanks, Berta.
Ordering a pizza and going home.
Two of the three things you want
in a woman.
And you wonder
why Chelsea dumped you.
I'll tell you what I wonder.
I wonder how you could
possibly get stoned enough...
...to stick your tongue
in the mouth of a 60-year-old woman.
Zing.
Boy, I just love this male bonding,
giving each other the old business.
The old business?
Yeah, you know,
the needle, the zets, the razzmatazz.
Herb, I gotta ask you something.
Are there any other guys
you hang out with?
Oh, sure. I have my peeps.
There's my water-polo league,
the guys down at the model-train shop.
Oh, and my barbershop quartet.
Although I can't have them over anymore.
Why not?
Four-part harmony
triggers Judith's migraines.
Plus, mustaches creep her out.
Not just mustaches,
any facial hair whatsoever.
- Right, except eyebrows.
- Neatly trimmed.
Right, the two-finger rule.
Huh. Chelsea had a two-finger rule.
Nothing to do with eyebrows though.
All right, I'll see you later.
- Where you going?
- To the pier with Celeste.
- Who's Celeste?
- My girlfriend. She lives next door.
- She pretty?
- She's gorgeous and smart and popular.
- No kidding.
- We don't get it either.
- Maybe she's punishing her father.
- Let's hope so.
I'm just the stepdad here, but shouldn't you
tell him what time to be home?
I don't have to. I know her father.
Hey, Jake.
Hello, sir.
Celeste, Jake's here.
So how have you been?
We're walking to the pier, we're gonna
play Skee-Ball, and we'll be back by 11.
You're damn right you will.
- Come on, it's freezing out here.
- Shouldn't we put out the cigars?
Why?
Uh, because we're not allowed to smoke
in the house?
It's my house.
We can smoke cigars,
we can smoke salmon, whatever we want.
Are you sure?
Relax, no whiny broad
is gonna nag at you.
Herb, make sure you use an ashtray
and a coaster.
I stand corrected.
Zing.
Gotcha.
Oh, this is gonna be a long night.
- Hi, Charlie.
- Oh, God.
- What did the little knucklehead do?
- Nothing. Jake said you were hanging out.
- I thought you might want company.
- Come on in.
I baked snickerdoodles, if you're hungry.
- You baked snickerdoodles?
- Yeah. Why's that funny?
It's not.
You know Alan, and this is Herb.
- Hi.
Make yourself comfortable.
Something to drink?
I wouldn't say no to an appletini.
An appletini? Ha, ha.
My brother drinks appletinis.
Why is that funny?
It's not.
One appletini, coming up.
He can get away with it. You can't.
So how do you know Charlie and Alan?
- Oh, I'm married to Alan's ex-wife.
- No kidding. And you hang out?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
Wow. I couldn't be friends with the man
who's putting it to my ex.
Well, to be fair,
there hasn't been a lot of putting lately.
And after the baby's born,
there will be even less.
How's that possible?
Not only will she not let you touch her...
...she'll interrupt you
while you're touching yourself.
Oh?
I had to start showering at the Y.
- Okay, one appletini.
- Thank you.
- What are you guys talking about?
- Masturbating at the YMCA.
Really? Just talk, right?
Yeah, but the night is young.
So, Jerome...
...solve one of the great mysteries
of life for us.
What does your daughter see in Jake?
You know,
I've been asking myself the same thing.
Maybe she's punishing me.
- No offense.
- None taken.
We're way ahead of you.
You know, my wife and I are having a girl.
Any advice?
Yeah. Before your daughter starts dating,
um, bulk up.
Okay.
Boy, remember
when we first started dating?
Yup. Eighth grade, Louise Miller.
Oh, ninth grade, Maxine Chernakoff.
Sixth grade, Mrs. Terapotta.
It wasn't actually a date.
Nowadays, she'd probably go to jail.
So, what about you, Herb?
- What about me, what?
- Your first date. Junior high? High school?
Oh, college, freshman year.
I was kind of a geek in high school.
Hard to believe.
No, really. They called me Big Bird.
So, what happened in college?
I stopped wearing yellow shirts
and lowered my standards.
Okay, okay, here's one.
First sexual experience
that was not traditional intercourse.
- What are we talking about here?
- You know what I'm talking about.
Boy Scouts.
What?
Oh. Zing.
Alan, when did you
first take your oral exams?
I don't think I should say.
- Why not?
- I just don't.
- Come on, we're all friends. Who was it?
- Your wife.
So your first time doing that
was with Judith?
Hey, me too.
Me too.
Just kidding. Zing. Zing.
What is "zing"?
Is that some type of white-guy slang?
Quite possibly.
My barbershop quartet does a killer version
of "Zing! Went the Strings of My Heart."
Real showstopper.
Kind of like that story.
Zing.
Did I get that one right?
Oh, good. Finally.
- Hookers?
- Pizza.
Oh. That's nice too.
- Hey, Mr. Harper.
- Oh, hey, Gordon. It's been a long time.
- Yeah, two years.
- So, what you been up to?
Well, I finished night school...
...got my business degree,
met an amazing girl, got married...
...landed a great job as a stockbroker, the
company went under, my wife left me, uh...
...and that will be 28.50.
Oh, man, I'm sorry.
- You want a drink?
- Why stop now?
Come on in.
Hey, everybody, this is Gordon.
- His wife left him.
- Hey, Gordon.
- Welcome to the Losers' Lounge.
- Heh, heh. Glad to be here.
The topic of discussion
is first nontraditional sexual experience.
Bible camp.
- Where you guys want me to put these?
- Oh, here, let me move the snickerdoodles.
Oh, snickerdoodles.
- You don't like them?
- No, no, I do.
It's just that my wife used to call me
her little snickerdoodle. Heh, heh.
- You're kidding.
- Well, no, not all of me.
It was her little nickname for my, uh...
Oh, that is a terrible name for a penis.
- Oh, yeah? What did your wife call yours?
- Mr. Roundtree.
Richard Roundtree?
The guy who played Shaft?
- Oh, right.
- Oh, yes.
That's way better than "snickerdoodle."
Judith calls mine "that thing."
As in "Get that thing away from me"?
- Yeah, how did you know?
- Just a guess.
Okay, I'm out of here.
Where you going?
Someplace where I'm not knee-deep
in pathetic, penis-naming, sad sacks.
No offense.
- None taken.
Let's go, King Snake.
- What do you want?
- Just listen.
Rachel? Hey, it's Charlie.
Look, about the pictures you sent me-
No, no. No, they were very nice.
Yeah, real artsy.
But the thing is,
I'm kind of engaged now.
I am definitely engaged now,
so you shouldn't send me any more.
Doesn't matter who asked for them.
The point is, I am no longer interested
in anyone's boobs...
...other than my fiancée's.
No, I'm not gonna send you
a picture of hers.
Right?
No.
- Okay, take care.
- Thank you, Charlie.
I just want you to know
how much you mean to me.
Did you delete the pictures?
Um, I guess there's a case
to be made for that.
- What are you doing? Press delete.
- Hang on.
I'm imprinting them in my memory.
Delete, delete, delete. Look, I'm deleting.
GORDON & HERB Zing!
Dear, when you smiled at me
- Zing!
- I heard a melody
- It haunted me from the start
- The start
- The start
Zing!
- Something inside of me
- Started a symphony
Zing! Went the strings of my heart
Zing!
'Twas like a breath of spring
I heard a robin sing
Zing!
About a nest set apart
No wonder they're all alone.
Zing!
All nature seemed to be
- In perfect harmony
Zing! Went the strings of my heart
Who is the man that would risk his neck
For his brother man?
Shaft
Right on
- I heard this cat Shaft is one bad mother-
- Shut your mouth
- I'm talking about Shaft
- Then we can dig it
He's a complicated man
No, I can't do this.
She has to take me back.